stopcall.me 2016-04-06

# STOP CALL from Privacy Policy

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices, including how we collect and use the information you may provide to us on the Web site, and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Collected information**

When you submit information for publication on our Website, all information supplied will be available to the public. Please exercise caution when supplying personally identifying information. Avoid posting your own email address and phone number within the post message.

Like most other Internet sites, we use cookies to personalize and enhance your experience on our sites. No identifiable information is gathered via the cookies. We also use Internet traffic analysis software which tracks your visited pages.

**Information we collect:**

  * IP address;
  * Pages visited;
  * About Computer / Device (type, operating system, browser etc.).

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies are necessary to provide you with certain website features.

**Links to third party Web sites**

Our Website offers hyperlinks to other Web sites which may have information policies and practices different from ours. We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or the content of any third party Web sites. Once you've left our Web sites via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

**Third party advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Web sites. These companies may use cookies, pixel tags, or otherwise independently collect non-personally identifiable information from you and use this information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We do not control their collection and use of information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. Any modifications to our Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page.

**Questions and comments**

Questions regarding this privacy statement should be submitted via the [feedback form](http://www.stopcall.me/help/contact-us).
